<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="attraction_name">Title</string>

    <string name="maps_package_name">com.google.android.apps.maps</string>
    <string name="query">"?q="</string>
    <string name="geo">"geo:"</string>
    <string name="video">"video"</string>

    <string name="attraction">""attraction""</string>
    <string name="section_number">"section_number"</string>
    <string name="list">"list"</string>


    <string name="restaurants_title">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="hotels_title">Hotels</string>
    <string name="beaches_title">Beaches</string>
    <string name="museums_title">Museums</string>

    <string name="restaurant_name1">"Le Méditerranéen"</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name2">"le Petit Chalet"</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name3">"Bab Errayane"</string>
    <string name="restaurant_name4">"Le Corsaire"</string>

    <string name="restaurant_desc1">Le Méditerranéen restaurant is located in the Es Seddikia district, in the municipality of Oran.\n\n
        Specialty\n
        In a pleasant and warm setting, the restaurant Le Méditerranéen offers dishes based on fresh fish as well as innovative culinary dishes. The restaurant also offers meat dishes.\n\n
        Opening hours\n
        The restaurant is open from Saturday to Thursday from 11:30 to 15:00 and 18:30 to 23:30.\n\n
        On Fridays, it is open only in the evening.\n\n
        Rate\n
        Approximately 2500 dinars per person.\n\n
        Coordinates\n
        The Mediterranean restaurant\n\n
        Address: Mohamed Fertas Avenue, Haï Es-Seddikia, 31000, Oran, Algeria.\n\n
        Telephone: +213 (0) 41 42 95 13\n\
        Mobile: +213 (0) 560 00 41 00</string>

    <string name="restaurant_desc2">le Petit Chalet restaurant is a gastronomic establishment located in the municipality of Kristel about ten kilometers east of the city center of Oran.\n\n
        The restaurant is ideally located at the edge of a cliff with a magnificent view of the sea. The building, built in 1926 has several terraces with sea views.\n\n
        Specialty\nThe property mainly serves seafood dishes.\n\n
        Rate\nAround 2000 dinars per person.\n\n
        Coordinates\nThe Petit Chalet restaurant\n\nAddress: Ain Franine Road, Kristel, 31000, Oran, Algeria.\n\nTelephone: +213 (0) 542 35 66 47</string>

    <string name="restaurant_desc3">Bab Errayane is a fast food restaurant, located in the city center of Oran, on the very commercial street Khemisti.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_desc4">"Le Corsaire is located in the old quarter of Sidi El Houari, in the municipality of Oran, near the Promenade Ibn Badis and the Palais du Bey.\n\n
        The Corsair is considered the most famous seafood restaurant in Oran. It has a small outdoor terrace."</string>

    <string name="hotel_name1">"Sheraton"</string>
    <string name="hotel_name2">"Méridien"</string>
    <string name="hotel_name3">"Liberté"</string>
    <string name="hotel_name4">"Les Ambassadeurs"</string>

    <string name="hotel_desc1">"The Sheraton Hotel is a 5-star hotel located a short walk from the center of Oran in the Seddikia district overlooking the beautiful bay of Oran."</string>
    <string name="hotel_desc2">"Le Méridien is a luxury 5-star hotel located a few kilometers east of downtown Oran."</string>
    <string name="hotel_desc3">"The "Liberty Hotel" is a 4-star hotel establishment located in the area of seats near the University of Oran (USTO)."</string>
    <string name="hotel_desc4">"Les Ambassadeurs hotel is a 3-star hotel located in the district of Haï Karama in Oran."</string>

    <string name="beach_name1">Andalouses</string>
    <string name="beach_name2">Paradis Plage</string>
    <string name="beach_name3">Saint-Roch</string>
    <string name="beach_name4">La plage de Bomo</string>

    <string name="beach_desc1">"The Andalouses beach is located in the town of El Ançor, in the wilaya of Oran.\n\n
        It is shared between a private beach (fee) and a public beach (free). At the private beach, the rental of chairs, tables and umbrellas is possible around 200 to 400 dinars."</string>
    <string name="beach_desc2">"Paradis Plage is located between Bouisseville beach and Clairefontaine beach, in the municipality of Aïn El Turk, in the wilaya of Oran."</string>
    <string name="beach_desc3">Saint Roch is a beach located in the town of Ain El Turk, exactly between the tip of Saint Roch and the beach of Trouville. From the beach you will have a view of the Rock of the Old and the Djebel Santon.</string>
    <string name="beach_desc4">"Bomo beach is located between the beach of Coralès and the beach of Etoile, on the commune of Bousfer, in the wilaya of Oran."</string>

    <string name="museum_name1">Le musée « Ahmed Zabana »</string>
    <string name="museum_name2">"Le musée d'art moderne"</string>
    <string name="museum_name3">Le musée du Moudjahid</string>

    <string name="museum_desc1">The museum "Ahmed Zabana" is located in the district of Haï Sidi El Bachir in Oran.</string>
    <string name="museum_desc2">"The Museum of Modern Art (MAMO) is located on the famous street Larbi Ben M'Hidi in the historic heart of the city of Oran."</string>
    <string name="museum_desc3">The Mujahid Museum is located near the headquarters of Sonatrach and the Great Ibn Badis Mosque in Oran.</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="picture">picture</string>
</resources>
